Good morning if you're not shoveling out
your driveway right now. Welcome to
Drogram with Ted R and John Kuryaku.
It's Monday, January 26th. Thank you so
much for joining us. Uh good morning,
John. Nice to see you.
>> Ted, nice to see you, man. But this snow
situation is just not for me. Look at my
hair. And I didn't shave or anything.
>> Uh yeah. No, I I I I feel you for sure.
Um so uh but at least we're not in
Minneapolis where it's both hot and cold
at the same time.
>> And uh and um yeah, we're not in danger
so much of getting shot today as we
would be in
>> Minneapolis.
>> Probably not. No, probably not. Um so
we'll be getting into we'll dig in deep
into Minneapolis. Of course um the
military purge in China. Uh and uh some
breaking news out of u Gaza. Israel has
reopened or is reopening the Rafa border
crossing to Egypt. Uh what does that
mean? The Israelis are not promising
that this is a two-way trip. If you
choose to avail yourself of this
crossing, you may not be permitted to
return home. Um, John, should we do some
questions? Should we just Maybe we
should just talk launch into
Minneapolis. I mean,
>> sure.
>> I I gotta say, I mean,
>> so obviously I mean, in a way, you can't
even make this stuff up, right? First
they they shot a woman named Good. Now
they shot a guy named Pretty. Um, you
know what's next? Maybe the ice guys
start to rename have to start renaming
themselves as like [__] or [__]
Um, so anyway, the the thing is the uh
you know, you're starting to see the
cracks starting to to form. I mean, the
administration and its allies have been
stonewalling like crazy uh for the last
like few weeks as this crisis has spun
out of control. All they've done is
added more fuel to the fire by sending
in more ICE agents to Minneapolis where
they are obviously not doing a good job
to say the least. And um so now uh you
know the the usual stonewalling just
doesn't seem to be working anymore. Um
Republicans are start in the in the
House of Representatives and uh and in
the Senate are starting to uh make
threats about uh possibly uh causing a
government shutdown uh on Saturday,
January uh 31st, right? Um they're
they're going to
>> senator
>> uh they want to withhold funding. They
wanted to alakart it and just have a
vote where they could vote for the whole
budget except for Homeland Security, but
then they decided not to. The
Republicans said, "No, we will not do
that. You either vote for the whole
thing or you don't vote at all." Looks
like I mean, I don't know with the way
that they caved on the uh on the ACA
subsidies. Who knows if the Democrats
are capable of following through on a
threat, but um you know, the point is
you can definitely see the narrative
changing. the New York Post, which is
Rupert Murdoch's right-wing Oregon in
New York, um, you know, they over the
weekend they literally on a couple of
occasions stopped covering the story in
Minneapolis, even though it's obviously
the lead story in the nation in every
media outlet. And today, their lead
story is about Minneapolis, and it's all
right-wingers and Republicans uh,
basically calling for investigations or
saying that ICE should leave
Minneapolis. I mean, clearly they have
lost this narrative. I mean, I I tweet I
I think this feels like a Kent State
moment for the administration.
>> You took the words right out of my
mouth. This is this is Governor Rhodess
and Kent State all over again. And I
want to add too that
if it looks like a cover up and it
smells like a cover up, it's cover up.
But the thing is is there's no statute
of limitations on murder. And so Donald
Trump can pretend all he wants that this
guy pretty was the aggressor. We watched
the video. This guy was executed in cold
blood in full view of a hundred people.
And it's on tape. And so Donald Trump's
not going to be president forever.
Eventually the state is going to be
allowed or be able to conduct an
investigation, a real investigation. The
FBI is going to be ordered to to
cooperate. ICE is going to be ordered to
cooperate and people are going to go to
prison.
>> But it's going to be hard, right, for
prosecutors and investigators. Evidence
has been um has disappeared, will have
disappeared. It will have been
destroyed. Uh witnesses will have um
moved away, been hard to locate, will
have died.
>> Yes.
But yeah, I mean, so I mean, by the way,
I mean, my take on what happened here is
that uh you know, there's there's
basically up to 10 ICE guys um you know,
basically on top of this dude. Um he
never pulled his gun ever, despite what
the what Republicans keep saying on
social media. He just there's no brand,
you know, if you bring a gun and you
brandish it as the cops, they can shoot
you. Sure, agreed. But he didn't. And so
um so anyway the um he he's so my take
is he they take the gun away from him
and because these are not cops and
they're not trained properly they don't
scream the guy doesn't who takes the gun
should shout clear
>> but he doesn't there's not you know and
instead someone maybe him maybe someone
else shouts gun probably another one and
at that point they all open fire because
they they think they're under threat Um,
>> and when they open fire, man, they don't
shoot once.
>> No,
>> they shoot back.
>> Yeah.
>> The guy's lying on his stomach. Um, you
know, he's clearly been disarmed and he
never made a move for his gun. Um, I
don't think he would have made a no
matter what, uh, you know, Secretary
Gnome says, there's no way that he was
going to, uh, you know, his intent was
to confront law enforcement. Uh, you
know, his intent he was there. He was
recording like a lot of other people.
And then he was shocked when an ICE
agent gratuitously, brutally, viciously
shoved this woman for no reason
whatsoever. She's just standing there. I
mean, he's not she's not in his way.
He's not trying to get past her. Um, you
know, she doesn't bug him. Um, you know,
they this is for fun that they shove
her. And so, he's shocked. And like any
red-blooded American man who is raised
to defend women properly, he tries to
intercede and then they go after him.
>> It's exactly what happened. And you
know, another thing, too, is that
Minnesota is a concealed carry state.
>> He was perfectly within his rights to
have that gun on him. It is his
constitutional right to have a gun on
him.
>> By the way, what is it? Is the second
amendment is the right now trying to
argue that the second amendment only
applies if you're a right-wing
Republican?
>> Exactly. Because I mean it seems like
that's what they're arguing. Kyle
Writtenhouse, you know, showed up with a
with an AR-15 long gun at a protest. You
know, he crossed state lines. He didn't
even bring his own gun. Okay? He didn't
have any permit at all to have it
anyway. But the but he's a hero to the
right. um you know, right-wingers
brought guns to the Charlottesville
protesters protests, the Unite the
Right. They they argued this is totally
legit. I know it's a little creepy, but
it's our right. It's our second
amendment. Um so, how come the second I
mean I mean, are they so [__] that
they don't know that if the Second
Amendment can be stripped away for
liberals, it can be stripped away for
them, too. You know, after George Floyd
was killed, I tweeted um
and I did this in a in a moment of
anger. I said, "I urge every black man
in America to arm himself immediately."
And the fallout was ridiculous.
>> Black people the right to arm
themselves.
>> Exactly. It is their
>> probably need it more than the rest of
us do. And but it comes back to your
point that for for many on the right,
it's okay for them to be armed.
>> Mhm.
>> They want first and second amendment
rights.
>> They don't want anyone else to have
them.
>> Exactly.
>> But it's either for all of us or it's
for none of us. Yes.
>> The state would love to get rid of the
second amendment. They would love it.
>> Yes. Indeed.
>> I mean, you know, right-wingers who who
who play that narrative like, well,
don't bring a gun to a I mean, there's
many um you know, there's many
possibilities. I mean, I'm sure lots of
people in that crowd had guns. Um
>> I mean, it's Minneapolis.
>> Uh
>> Minneapolis, they're hunters there.
>> Yeah.
>> You know, a lot of people hunt.
>> Yeah. And and Minneapolis could be a
sketchy city. There's a lot of
carjacking. I mean, it's not a bad idea
to carry a gun.
>> You know, my brother once my brother
lived in Minneapolis for nine years. My
sister lived there for 15 years. And I
used to go up to to visit them in the
summertime. My brother played a gig one
time. This is before he became famous
and rich. Uh he played a gig and he
stopped at a gas station at like 2 2:30
in the morning to get gas. And he went
inside to pay. You couldn't pay at the
pump in those days. He went inside to
pay. And there was a woman behind the
register and she was just standing there
and she appeared to be very frightened.
And there was a guy standing off to the
side just kind of standing there. And my
brother whispered to her, "Are you
okay?" And she just nodded and he said,
"Do you want me to call the cops?" And
she went like this. As soon as my
brother drove away, that man killed her.
>> Oh, Jesus Christ.
>> He was her aranged boyfriend. She had
broken up with him. He hunted her down
at her place of work and he killed her.
My brother was identified through the
security cameras and um and ended up
having to testify at the trial and uh
while he was on the stand, the guy just
screamed out from the defendant's table,
"I should have killed you when I had the
chance."
>> That that must have really helped with
the jury.
>> Guilty.
>> Yeah. Good. I hope he never gets out.
>> Yeah. Minneapolis is like any other big
city. It's got serious problems.
>> Yeah. Yeah. By the way, Ron Kubie, the
famous um left-wing attorney friend of
mine on my Facebook, he said uh you
know, I I'm I'm thinking that now the
Minneapolis police has a has an ethical
duty to def use deadly force if
necessary to defend the citizens of
Minneapolis against ICE. I mean, if ICE
is gratuitously gunning people down,
>> you know, I mean, I think he's right. I
I think
>> they have to agree. I mean, you know,
basically ICE you can't view them
anymore as like, well, they're they're
they're not really law enforcement
officers. They're criminals.
>> They're not. And and you know, it's
>> they're they're the rioters here. By the
way, I I love how basically Fox News
keeps saying rioters and then they'll
show the vid they'll show the video of a
crowd and there's no flames. No one's
even running. People are standing still.
I mean, has they have they forgotten
what riots look like? I know what riots
look like. LA was a riot. That's not a
riot.
>> Got that right. Yeah.
>> These are peaceful protests.
>> And you know, the the founding fathers
gave us the second amendment to protect
ourselves against tyranny, including
government tyranny,
>> especially government tyranny.
>> Especially.
>> Yeah. Um, all right. Let's show I know
Robbie has a few thoughts about this. He
doesn't. And I think we should we should
bring him in
>> if he wants to talk about it.
Who? Me? No. Never.
>> No. It's not like I have opinions. No. I
was watching a lot of the videos for
what happened with this guy and I know
that he was carrying a Sig and most Sigs
do not have a safety. A lot of them the
several models do. Most of them don't.
They kind of go along with the with the
Glock model.
>> Yeah. There's even been some lawsuits
about this.
>> Yeah. Well, I mean it just depends on,
you know, how proficient you are with
firearms. But I I have a Jericho 941.
It's the Desert Eagle. No, that that J
that John wants to get. I've got mine in
40 because I'm in Montana. We got bears.
9 millimeters. It's gonna piss a bear
off. A 40 will do the job.
>> That's right. Uh, the reason why I bring
this up is that whenever you whenever
you carry a a semiotic semi-ac pistol,
the default once you put the magazine in
is that you have one round in the
chamber. And then, of course, the
magazine is full. U, if your gun has a
safety, you turn the safety on. It's
called condition two. If you don't have
a safety, you're automatically condition
three. So, what that means is you pull
the trigger, it goes off. It looked like
what happened that the ice guy who
disarmed this this pretty guy had no
trigger discipline. His glove
was was right there on the trigger
guard. He discharged the gun. He shot he
shot the pistol. That's the first shot
that you heard. Then the ice guys lit
this guy up for no reason at all. The
fact that
the Trump administration is lying about
this and they are lying about this.
Somebody just said if they were properly
trained, they didn't give him a chance.
Like, sir, could you please hand over
your firearm? The guy snatched it.
Right.
>> Well, of course. Well, that's See,
here's a big part of the problem. I
support what I doing. We need mass
deportations like to the scales of of of
hundreds of millions of these people
need to go away. That's that's my that's
my state.
>> There are not hundreds of millions of
>> figure it out. Millions in. We'll round
it down. Millions then. Fair enough.
>> Mhm. So, if you can be a deportation
hawk like I am and not and not have a
militarized police force, if you are if
if you're a cop, but you're dressed like
a soldier and you're trained like a
soldier, besides you're trained at all.
And if you're armed like a soldier,
you're going to act like a soldier.
Soldiers don't make good cops. That's
the whole problem. That's the issue.
And the fact that Trump and and his
alkalites on right-wing media are going
out
and saying they sound like gun control
Democrats. Well, why you car taking a
gun to a protest? Because it's my right
as an American citizen. That's why. If
you don't exercise a right, you lose it.
That's the whole point.
And the fact that Trump is pushing this,
it's lost him gun owners of America.
It's lost him the NRA. he is blowing up
what's left of his coalition and uh it
it's really starting to show who are
just rep just uh Republicans and and
real honest to god right-wingers who
actually value what the constitution
says. Jack Persobic is a complete
sellout. Matt Walsh, same thing. They
they go and they pretend like they're
small government, you know,
right-wingers. They want to be me.
They're not me. These are Republican
sickopants and you can tell it by their
rhetoric.
>> I have a message for the right-wingers,
right? Like, and I just tweeted this out
this morning. Like, listen, I know you
don't want to become Democrats to fight.
This is this is a fascist state. It's a
state that is rising into fascism. It's
feeling and looking like Germany in
1933, 1934, where you still have the
veneer of like constitutional law that
they inherited. You still have the old
judges. You still have the courts, the
cops, but you're ignoring those laws
because you now want to do whatever you
want to do. That's the rise of fascism.
It's state violence, right? Like if you
want to fight that and be against that,
you don't have to become a Democrat. You
have to become a leftist. And they're
not the same. But you don't have to
become a Democrat. I'm not a Democrat.
Become a leftist.
>> Well, here's the big problem though,
Ted, is that people on your side of the
aisle have been calling people like me
on my side aisle Nazis for
>> No, we haven't. Not us. That was that
was the Democrats.
>> Okay. Well, then y'all need to do a
better job with your branding.
>> Democrats are the biggest enemy of the
left. They're worse than the right.
>> But see, I mean, here's here's the
biggest problem, though. Is like, for
example, let's say we go with the Ted
Roll model. We abolish ICE. What happens
next? Just great amnesty.
>> I'm not saying no, no, no, no. Just so
you know, like uh if the Soviet Union,
you know, communist commun, you know, a
socialist country, they vigorously
defended their borders and deport and
deported illegal aliens. And you might
say nobody snuck in. Oh, people snuck
in. No, they didn't. From places like
Afghanistan and they were like,
you're not a nation state unless you
have you need some sort of entity that
does what ICE does, but just not the way
they're doing it.
>> I agree. But I'll tell you right now,
the reason why so many people on the
right are willing to give people give
ICE a pass, at least up until now before
that Trump shows real colors and show
that he's not only a [__] but he's a
fascist
is
>> and he surrounded himself with fascists,
which is actually more concerning.
>> Oh, for sure. I mean, he doesn't have
anyone that that that disagrees with
him. The issue that we have is let's
just assume that ICE gets defunded,
everything else happens. What happens to
the migrants that are here? Reagan gave
us an amnesty 40 years ago and things
have only gotten worse. If you're if
you're on the right like me, you see
this is the one chance, the only shot
that we have.
>> I get it.
>> To get mass deportation.
>> That's such a croc. Robbie Obama
deported far far more people than Donald
Trump ever deported. And you guys were
unhappy then
>> because he didn't deport enough.
He deported a factor of how many times
more than what Trump deported?
>> No, I agree with you and and and that's
one of the that's one of the things I
asked know Ted on Twitter yesterday is
that where were the lefties protesting
when Obama was doing this or he get it
passed because of his skin color.
>> Yeah. No. Well, maybe maybe he did. No,
I I agree that you got to follow the you
got to follow the law here. There's a
way to to immigrate to this country and
it's got to be within the confines of
the law. But but but Obama was the
deorter chief and and we're not talking
about deportations. This isn't a
question of deportations. It's a
question of federal overreach.
>> No, I agree. Oh, I'm right there with
you. But I'm telling you right now
though, this is why that a lot of people
So
>> Donald Trump has has has completely he
has shot you in the back in the same way
that he shot Alex pretty because he has
discredited the uh anti-immigrant nivist
uh you know nationalist whatever you
want to call it the idea to put America
first. He's discredited that whole idea
uh with these with with the you know by
basically creating ICE not as a
deportation force but as a goon squad.
>> I agree and and there needs to be major
reforms. This is someone who wants I
want every single immigrant in this
country deported.
>> I don't really think Donald Trump cares
that much about deporting illegal
immigrants. I think Donald Trump cares
about, you know, waving his dick around
and telling other people what to do and
making everyone scared scared to death
of him and his government.
>> Yeah. And and I wish I could say you're
wrong, but you're not.
>> I think that you're right. I think what
this is is that Trump just wants to
whatever reason, he wants to just he he
wants a strong centralized
federal executive. That's what he wants.
And as a right-winger, that's the
absolute last thing that I want. And as
John pointed out last week, um, you
know, before before the weekend about
his, uh, meeting with Ilhan Omar, you
know, the Democrats are salivating.
That's what you said, John. They're
salivating to inherit this uh, you know,
executive powerful imperial executive
branch.
>> They won't change anything. Hey guys,
>> we need to thank uh some people here.
Sodon
>> Sodon, thank you. Thank you for $50. He
says, John Ted, good morning. What would
we rebuild public trust for this
administration right now? I feel sick to
my stomach about this and I feel so it's
going to get worse because of who the
president has in his ear. This is true
sad.
>> Absolutely, totally completely agree.
>> Well, what would Let's answer his
question. What would we build trust?
Well, first of all, as you know, it's a
cliche for a reason because it's true.
Uh, you know, trust is is is hard to
build and easy to to to destroy. Um,
look, I think the credibility of the
administration is in the toilet. Um, and
I think that the the crisis management
response here would be twofold. If I'm
advising the president, it would be
first of all, come clean. Be JFK after
the Bay of Pigs. Go to the American
people and just say, I was rotten. We,
my people and I, we lied. We weren't
fair. It's got to change. We can't go
after. We can't treat people like this.
Uh that doesn't mean anything about but
we still the policy is still the policy
but we're going to do it better. I think
also he's got a he's some heads got a
role. Um he's got to probably get rid of
the press secretary and Christino
and uh firmware. Thank you uh for $5.
There are per DHS 11 million so-called
illegals uh in uh in the US 330 million
citizens. That's less than 3%. this is a
non-pro but is used to uh illicit
hatred. I have to agree.
>> I don't know that it's a nonpro. I mean,
you know, 3% like uh you know, 3% can
really affect the unemployment rate if
you think about it, right? I mean, the
unemployment rate, the official
unemployment rate is around 4%, right? I
mean, 3%'s not insignificant.
>> Yeah. But also consider, I I agree, but
also consider how many of those jobs are
jobs that Americans just simply won't
take. I know Robbie has disagreed with
me on this in the past.
>> Yeah, I'm on team Robbie here.
>> How many how how many Americans are
willing to pick fruit in the fields in
California or work in the Purdue plants
in North Carolina?
>> You got to pay them, John.
>> Pay them.
>> I mean, it's like it's like anything. I
mean, I don't understand like, you know,
hey, I would love my own hovercraft,
but, you know, I can't afford one. So, I
don't have one. Well, if if and if I'm
an employ if I want to start a business
and you know, let's say I'm a farmer, I
want to hire I want to have strawberries
picked. Well, it's like and I want to
hire dudes to do it. I got to pay I gota
I got to find out what is the minimum
amount of money that people will take to
do that for me. How is that, you know?
So, if you and if you can't afford that,
then you can't afford to farm. The end.
>> Yeah. But then it's the same people who
are going to [__] about about food
prices. Well, I mean, prices will go up
with uh, you know, more expensive labor.
That's inevitable.
>> Right now, though, the issue is that
prices are going up, but wages aren't.
>> I mean, that's that's the whole issue.
>> I don't think immigration is the is the
only reason here. I think it's it's I
think it's a tertiary reason at best,
but it's still, you know, it's a
contributing factor. I mean, the thing
is, look, it it drives here's a here's a
truism, right? It is my entire life. It
has always been hard to find a job in
the United States of any kind. No matter
how well educated or you know or or
charming or anything you are, getting
work is hard. Getting good work is
almost impossible. Uh getting work that
allows you to pay your bills and maybe
save almost impossible. More impossible
than that. That's always been true. So
you you put people in that situation and
people might be like, "Well, we're all
in it together. That's just how it is.
But when you start importing foreigners
and then they're you're competing
against them, that makes people see red.
That's why they're so pissed.
And one thing I want to point out here
because I see a lot of comments of
people calling me a racist. I want to
make something incredibly clear here. My
stance on immigration has absolutely
nothing to do with the color of your
skin. I don't care if you're mass
importing people from Poland or from
Germany. As long as you have one
undermploy, undermployed or unemployed
American wants a job, the last thing you
should do is be importing know how many
tens of thousands or whatever, whatever
the number is. Who the hell knows at
this point to compete with those
Americans trying to get that work?
That's the whole issue for me. It's
economic. We have Americans living under
every single bridge in this country. We
have Americans who are underemployed. We
have Americans who are working two or
three jobs because they can't make
enough to to
>> Three of them are right here, by the
way.
>> This has nothing.
This has to do with rebuilding the
American workers.
Listen, here's the whole issue.
>> NAFTA hollowed out the entire middle of
the country. immigration hollowed out
the southern aggre the southern
agricultural field.
So you have all this so you have all
these people who are coming in legally
and illegally. Corporations want it
because they want to drive down the
wages. Now one thing that needs to be
that needs to be brought up. I think if
you're an employer and if you hire an
illegal, you should go to prison.
>> I mean that sincerely because
>> you have a problem with that
>> because you are ripping off the the
you're ripping off everybody. You're rip
the government's not the government's
not getting taxes for a lot less. I'm
I'm looking for one of them right now.
>> So I mean this is not just on the
migrant. No,
I understand the impetus of wanting to
come in and get a better life for your
person if the country that you live in
sucks.
>> Yeah, that's my disagreement with you me
Robbie is that you're you seem to not
always be sympathetic to the fact
>> because I'm not.
>> Those people are being used and and
cheated and exploited just like the rest
of us. I agree and that's why I have no
problem at all with throwing the
business owners in into the goolog.
Maybe send them to uh to the tender
embrace of northwest Montana or to the
or to the tundra of Alaska
>> supply side uh prosecutomics.
>> Yeah. I mean no make it happen. But the
point of case is is that we keep that
the argument that John you just made
these are people who are doing jobs that
Americans won't do. It's because you're
not paying the Americans to do the jobs.
Are wages going will prices go up if you
start paying people what they're worth?
The answer is yes. But what else is
going to go up? Wages. And right now
that's the problem. This is not a racial
argument. This is not a ra This is not a
racial thing. This has to do with
economics.
We are import We are importing. How many
How many thousands of coders do you have
from India to come in do jobs?
>> Oh no. That drives me absolutely insane.
>> Are too stupid to code?
>> Excusable.
>> Yeah. Are Americans too are Americans
too stupid to work on farms?
>> No, they're not. Some of them are just
like the sin of being over 35 years old.
So Silicon Valley won't hire them.
>> Yeah. And calling me a racist isn't
really winning the argument. What you're
doing is you're proving that you can't
compete with mine.
>> Um Robbie, thank you very much. We will
see you again. Let me know if you have
if we have an ad. Okay. So, uh we got
some more comments to get through here.
Um John McGuire, great question for you.
John, I see that some ICE agents are
taking the whistles and words personally
and and respond as they would in a bar
fight. John, what kind of training did
you receive to not take things
personally? And it's so true, right?
Like I mean, and that's by the way one
of the defenses, one of the the Fox
people say like, you know, they call
them names. They're under a lot of
pressure. I talk about snowflakes.
>> But I mean, they're babies, right? But
it's like, okay, but but it's true. I
mean, you got to get training to be like
to let it, you know, let it roll off
like, you know, like the off the off the
feathers of a duck. So, yeah. What What
did you Did you get training?
>> Yeah. The the training was to run. Run
away. Seriously, they used to tell us
all the time, get off the X. If you feel
like you are being drawn into something
that could spin out of control or put
you in over your head, run away.
And they they would just beat this into
us. There is no shame in running because
what's the alternative? You shoot
somebody in the head.
>> I remember one instructor saying
>> or they shoot you.
>> Yeah. Or they shoot you. Even worse. I
remember one instructor saying, "Do you
have any idea how much paperwork is
involved when you shoot someone?"
>> Exactly.
>> Yeah. That's that's very true. Um Yeah.
>> Get off the X and get out.
That was the training.
>> Thank you very much for the 50 bucks,
John Magcguire. I should take a page
from the IRS. The IRS jails 500 people a
year. Every year they collect more money
than owed. If the IRS started hauling
old ladies in for unclaimed bingo
winnings, they would lose their mandate.
Paperwork is more powerful than physical
force. And that's how this was pretty
much done, right? I mean, until until
now. I mean, it's not like we, like you
pointed out, John, under Obama, many
more people were deported. This was
handed handled administratively. I mean,
and like you can, if people run away,
you know, like you would say,
>> you can catch them. I mean, we live in a
surveillance state. We have license
plate trackers. We have facial
recognition software all over the place.
You I mean, most the vast illegal
immigrants cause, you know, commit real
crimes at a lower rate than American
citizens. So, it's like they're not
really dangerous to have them out on the
lamb. Just like pick them up later when
you have the chance.
>> Yes, it's true.
>> Um,
>> also another thing is if you're going to
deport people, I think they're more
deportable if they know like you would
give them three months to like finalize
their affairs and sell their stuff and
ship stuff home rather than think
they're going to be snatched off the
street at a moment's notice while their
kid is in school waiting for you to pick
them up, you know?
>> Yeah, that's rough. Um
um Soden, thanks for the 1999. The
reason why Obama deported so many is
because many of them had a final order
of deportation. ERO wasn't picking
people up from the car wash. They were
deporting criminal aliens who had
extensive criminal records. I mean that
more so than this. Yes. Although not
exclusively by any means. And that was
the theory of the Obama policy.
>> That's right.
Why do you think, Ted,
>> why do you think that there wasn't
really much in the way of an objection
when Obama was do I remember when Obama
was deporting all these people and
people even back then were calling him
the deorter and chief and nobody really
seemed to care. Why was that?
>> Um I think there was a lot I I think
there's hidden nivism on the among
liberals too who feel like Robbie does
about like they don't like competing
with these people for jobs. But, you
know, the victims, the deportes, um,
they were Latino, like overwhelmingly,
right? And white America didn't care.
And also, look, um, when a Democrat is
the president, the the brunch Democrats
don't say [__] about the abuses or
anything nasty that the Democrat does.
They didn't sh say [__] you know,
they're the same people who are pissed
off about the Venezuelan boat dronings
gave no [__] about the Wizeristani
uh you know um car dronings, right? They
did not care. And so basically like when
your guy that you voted for is the
president, you just basically close your
eyes and you turn a blind eye to
everything they do. And then you scream
about the very same things when the
other guy becomes president. It's team
politics. I [__] hate it. I don't
know if there's any way to get rid of
it, but it's just like we're stuck with
it.
>> Yeah. Yeah, that's right.
>> Accident. Thanks so much. Uh is that
Swedish Swedish uh Corona? Um
>> I think it is.
>> I think it is. I always think is that
Swedish or is that Seneagalles? Anyway,
uh thanks for the 200 whatever they are.
As a must be Sweden. As a European
working in border policing and irregular
migration, I'm quite appalled by what's
happening in the US and how ICE operates
right now. Even our civilian border
guards have a longer training than the
ICE agents. And you know, I love the
fact that they chose the 47 day training
period because Trump is the 47th
president. I'm like, you know, by the
way, I wouldn't have a problem if they
had chosen 47 months. Four years isn't
really too long, I don't think. I mean,
you know, you send you need four years
to graduate with an English degree with
a bachelor's, you know. I mean, you you
need three years to go to law school.
longer. You need longer training to
become a barber,
>> right? Yeah, that's true. I mean, beauty
school requires Yeah, but school
>> requires less time.
>> Tariq, thanks for the fiverr. I know you
touched base on it, but shocked, but how
shocked were you with Carney's uh Mark
uh yeah, Mark Carney from Canadia, his
Davos speech. Was it lip service to us
Canadians or is it a changing of the
tide? I'm really glad he asked that
question.
>> That's a good question. What did you
think of Mark Carney's um kind of
uncharacteristic uncannadian like
>> [__] you to the US?
>> It was sharp. Um I don't think it was
just
ju just to drill Donald Trump. I think
that I think that Carney really is
laying out a separate path. Uh I think
that the underlying message is that the
United States cannot be trusted as a
long-term partner anymore. And so it's
time for Canada to start looking out for
Canada. And if that means closer trade
ties with China, then there will be
closer trade ties with China. And don't
forget that
regardless of who happens to be in the
White House, whether it's a Democrat or
a Republican, we have put all kinds of
pressure on the Chinese to essentially
wreck their relations with with China.
I'm sorry. Uh we've been put putting
this pressure on the Canadians to wreck
their relations with China because it's
good for US policy. You know, we want
the the Canadians, for example, to grab
the CFO of CFO of Huawei and charge her
with some kind of stupid computer
hacking charge or whatever it happened
to be and then keep her in house arrest
for three years and then say, "Okay, you
can you can trade her for something
else."
The Canadians are tired of being used as
a as a bargaining chip for for US China
relations.
>> I also took it as a wakeup call to other
>> Absolutely. This was a slap at the
Americans and it's about time that
Canada took that swing.
>> Yeah. But I thought also it was like to
the Europeans and the rest of the world
like wake up. It's not things are not
the way they've always been. We got to
do we got to do it differently from now
on. Um all right. Listen, we got an ad,
John. So go ahead and read that. Still
haven't tried 1775 coffee? Now's your
shot. The 1775 starter kit just dropped.
Only a thousand units. You're getting
the bold dark roast that hits hard. The
smooth medium roast and the vitality
mushroom coffee for clean energy and
laser focus. No crash. All single origin
small batch toxin free and mold-free.
Plus, you're also getting a gold spoon
clip because freedom isn't scooped with
plastic. A frother strong enough to stir
up your coffee and your mother-in-law's
opinions. And a black 1775 tumbler. 170
bucks worth of coffee and gears. Yours
for 99. This is for the ones who've been
watching 1775 blow up on Rumble,
wondering if it's actually worth it.
Spoiler, it is. And Robbie says it's
worth it, too. Go to 1775
coffee.com/studio
and grab your starter kit before they're
gone. Bold beans, clean fuel, and a
morning routine that stands for
something just like Rumble does. Um,
okay. Uh, firmware 10 bucks. Thanks
much. Uh, humans react to the gut, not
the head. Just ask Edward Bernay, Joseph
Gerbles, Joe McCarthy, etc. Good people
like Robbie are being used by
neofascists to create divisions and
facilitate evil. I don't know about
people like Robbie. I think Robbie
understands what's going on.
>> Robbie just disagrees with us. That's
that's
>> Well, I think Robbie's just like he's
he's I'll let Robbie speak for himself.
Robbie, you're correct me if I'm wrong,
but my my take is you want to see mass
deportations, but you're not happy about
the way this is going and you're kind of
hoping that somehow the mass deportation
regime can be saved without I mean just
I mean the hearts and minds of the
American people here. Uh Bob Guerrilla
editorial cartoons, right-winger, he was
on Facebook yesterday. I was reading
older guy and uh very right-wing and he
said look uh I remember I remember mi
it's like once the he's like I supported
the war but once the hearts and minds of
the American people have turned against
you there's nothing you can [__] do
>> over
>> and this is one of those moments. I mean
I think that's what you're kind of like
worried about here.
>> Yeah. I mean I want mass street
deportations but not the expense of a
police state. I mean, I if I got if I
got have one or the other,
>> um I I would rather just let just let
wages continue to stagnate and just let
the American economy implode and they'll
just selforrect. I don't want
>> the borders, open police state or open
borders. You'll take you'll take open
borders.
>> Yeah. Because at the end of the day,
>> so you're not being used.
>> No, I mean it's a fundamental
disagreement. Of the of the three people
here on this panel, I'm the only one
that's probably lost a job due to
illegal immigration.
I think that's probably fair to say.
>> Also,
>> although we don't know about jobs we
haven't been offered because of illegal
immigration, right?
>> Yeah. That's a great unknown. That's
something you'll that she'll never know.
And another thing I like to point out is
that immigration disproportionately, you
know, hurts black people because those
immigrants are competing, you know, with
jobs that that typically went to black
Americans. Yeah. I mean, no work that's
that's undeniably a fact.
>> I have a black wife.
I know that that's gonna surprise some
of y'all who think I'm a white supremist
or something, but I mean, it is what it
is. For me, this is not racial,
>> which means you live in a black
supremist household.
>> Oh, we have some pretty wild
discussions. I mean, Ted, you've been
here.
>> I mean, it it's it's it's wild. But I
mean,
what the American people have lost the
ability and and this really really
hurts. We have lost the ability to reach
across the aisle
in a populist way and discuss things
that actually can will affect the lives
of every single American regardless of
of of race or creed. And we sacrifice on
the altar of racism and the intellectual
dishonesty.
>> Oh, I I want wages to go up.
>> My son I want to be able to one day be
able to buy a house.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> He can't do that now.
>> Yeah. I mean, you're if listen, if if
you're trying to push a 50-year mortgage
because there's enough inventory and
you're importing tens of thousands of
people, you know,
>> don't get me started inventory [__] We
don't need to build more houses. All
right. Thanks, Robbie. Um, anyway, uh,
okay. So, uh, Brad Weir, thanks for the
fiber. How much does the
military-industrial complex contribute
to inflation and the debasement of our
currency? That's a super complicated
question. That's a good question. You
know, I I'm not an economist, of course,
and you probably have um a better mind
for economics than I do, but it seems to
me that when when the
military-industrial complex makes so
many new millionaires,
>> that is going to fuel inflation,
especially in in things like uh real
estate. You know, I I've I've said
before that
20 years ago, I was middle middle class.
My new wife was middle middle class and
we bought a house in a in a middle
middle class area of Arlington,
Virginia. We tore it down and we built a
nice house in which to raise our family.
Well, now in our neighborhood, the
average house,
which is the tear down that we bought,
is $2.4 million.
If you want a house like what we built,
it's three 3.2 million. My children will
never be able to live in the
neighborhood in which they grew up. It's
not possible. And it's not going to turn
around. It's not like housing prices are
going to come down.
>> No. No. If that happens, I mean, I would
love that to happen except for the fact
that it would mean we're in a
depression.
>> That's right. That's right. So, yeah,
it's like as soon as as soon as the
planes hit those towers and the
Pentagon, everybody started getting rich
in the Washington area. I mean the
problem with I mean in a broad
macroeconomic sense right the problem
with military with militarism is that
you're re you're allocating societal
resources into products that have very
low or negative value added I mean you
know like for example you sell a car
well that that's value added people use
that car and actually you know someone
who buys a car might make more money
because they could for example get a job
that they can drive that car to um but
mill you know um you build uh you know,
a a predator drone. Uh it it it's going
to go obsolete within a few years. Yeah.
And the Hellfire missiles that it fires
are either going to be blown up
somewhere or are going to again become
obsolete and then they're going to go
into a landfill and pollute the earth.
And then um there's a there's obviously
to the extent that deficit spending
contributes to inflation, which is not
100%, you know, true, but it's partly
true. I mean, God, I mean, half of all
deficit spending in this country is
caused by the military-industrial
complex, maybe more, at least, right? At
least half the federal budget. So, I
mean, it's for sure it's having an
inflationary effect. Um,
hey you, thanks for the five bucks.
Loved your appearance on Tinfoil Hat,
John. Followed you here because of that.
Keep exposing the truth, corruption, and
scouts. I appreciate you. Firmware five
bucks. Not true, Robbie. I've lost jobs
to Asian immigrants, tech jobs because
Asian labor is cheaper.
>> Very true.
>> True.
>> Um,
>> unsung Pat five bucks. Any thoughts on
Macron's agent Smith Agent Smith
impersonation speech
Davos? I've been thinking about it and I
conclude that he had a he had a shiner
courtesy of Mrs. Mcron.
>> I mean,
>> you think that's true, huh? It's either
that or he has this thing that, you
know, I have this like sunburn on the
retina thing. But you don't have to have
you don't have to look like Joe Biden
with the with the with the aviator dark
aviator glasses to handle that. Just
like you can just have tinted lens or
graduated lens like I have. That'll take
care of that. Ask an opthalmologist. So,
it's like it's either look, he either
has an eye problem or he's got something
he's covering up. Those are the two
possibilities. So, you know, I think
odds of eye problem low. You know, we
know that he gets hit by Mrs. Macron. I
mean, she punches him. She slaps him.
She He should divorce her ass. And uh
and I mean this very serious sincerely.
He should divorce her ass, make a public
statement and and basically create a
moment um that represents for abused men
and say honestly we need
>> Can you imagine what a scandal that
would be?
>> It'd be great. I mean we need that
moment. We need like the you know the
Magic Johnson I have AIDS moment. um you
know, which made it like, oh, people
with AIDS aren't, you know, aren't to be
uh reviled anymore because if Magic
Johnson, he's too charming. We can't we
can't hate Magic Johnson. Um even if we
don't really quite believe his story
about how he got it. Um you know, I
mean, it's it's like that. I don't know.
I that What do you think, John? What do
you think happened there?
>> Honestly, I think she hits him.
>> Yeah,
>> I do. I think she hits him. And I never
I never believed that until until the
scene at the top of the airplane steps.
>> It was clearly she was hitting him. It
was clear, I should say, that he was
hitting him.
>> So yeah, I think he's an abused spouse.
>> But can you imagine
>> send her to prison?
>> You're the president of the what is it?
The fifth republic or whatever they call
themselves. You're the president
himself. He's a major world leader and
his wife beats on him.
>> Yeah. Not to mention also he's younger
and better looking than she is. Yeah,
>> you know, he's a great looking guy. I
mean,
>> he's very, very handsome man. That's
right.
>> I mean, that's probably why she hits
him,
>> right? So he doesn't like get too big
for his bridges and run off with like
some, you know, hot like singer
shooters,
>> which is what he should do.
>> Yeah, that's right.
>> Chess sniper 10 bucks. Thanks very much.
Robbie's wrong about immigration. I have
benefited greatly from German immigrants
who taught me a lot about engineering.
They had to be imported because the
Americans couldn't do the job or keep
up.
>> Look, I I love the immigrants that I've
met. My mother is an immigrant, okay? I
mean, it's like uh that's not the issue
here. I mean, Robbie's argument is that
it's it's just that immigration is used
to depress American wages.
And that's true. I mean, you know, I
mean, I'm I'm I wish there was way to
have immigration and not [__] over
American workers. But this goes back to
that idea that George W. Bush had that
he was negotiating with Vicente Fox, the
the president of Mexico in the days
before 911, the months before 911, where
we would begin granting these 9-month
work visas, mostly for menial work.
Um, they would pay taxes and have to go
back for three months to their home
countries and reapply.
Yeah,
>> that's we we should be we should have
renegotiated that, you know,
>> that's a better model. I have a feeling
that people like Robbie would not be
psyched about it, but it would certainly
be an improvement. Craig advanced. Ted,
you managed not to get into building
more houses to fight the cost. Well, get
into it, lol. We rent and are getting
kicked out of our house so they can
knock down our 1940s bungalow. Oh,
>> I mean, here's all I'm trying to say is
there are tens of millions of abandoned
units in the United States. Um, you
know, they should be seized under
eminent domain and given to Americans
who need a home. Uh, maybe I would say
the I love deals where it's like you get
this house for a hundred bucks, we're
going to come back in in five years and
you better have renovated it and if you
haven't, we're taking it away from you
and giving it to someone who can. But, I
mean, give people a chance. Like, by the
way, no property taxes on that. I mean,
we have so much aband I don't it's it's
unconscionable to be building new houses
from an ecological standpoint when
you've got so much so many abandoned
buildings all over the place.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Um that's right.
>> Uh let's see, Robbie, the problem, this
is from number six. The problem isn't
immigrants. The problem is that
billionaires have sold you the paradigm
that the immigrants took our jobs.
Billionaires are the problem. Fix it.
Well, I that's true, too.
>> I mean, you know, that's totally true.
>> Yeah. Um,
okay. Uh, Gregory Badis, CFA, there's a
lot of high-paying tech jobs that
Americans can't do because we don't have
the education for them. The Chinese and
the Indians are far more advanced in
that sector. We have to import talent.
Okay, listen. I don't believe that
because we have lots of undermployed
STEM graduates and and and people. But
even if that were true, why the in China
and and India, they don't treat um
college as a luxury commodity like a
[__] Lexus. It's like it's a, you
know, it's it's a necessity and it's
affordable and it's accessible to
anybody who's smart enough to get to
pass the admissions exam. We don't do
that here. I mean, so maybe make college
free or at least very affordable. um you
know before you start like it's
ridiculous like we don't let people get
a college education so they're working
at a [__] gas station instead of at
Google where they belong. Uh the whole
thing is is it's [__] up.
>> Um
>> so we should hit some international
stuff. Um one question here. Any
question any updates on Iran? Quadruple
J.
>> Yeah we should talk about Iran. Uh the
USS uh uh Abraham Lincoln carrier battle
group is uh in the Arabian Sea off the
coast of Oman.
I genuinely fear what's going to happen
in the coming weeks. I really do. And
the reason
>> big distraction from Minnesota,
>> big big distraction from Minnesota and
from the Epstein files which everybody
forgot existed.
>> True.
>> Um and that was the plan. So, I think
that I think that the Israelis and the
Americans genuinely smell blood in the
water and they believe rightly or
wrongly that all the Iranian government
needs is a gentle shove to collapse upon
itself. That's not going to be the case.
>> No,
>> exactly. There are
150,000 members of the um IRGC, the Iran
Revolutionary Guard Corps. Uh they are
the backbone of Iranian national
security. And if the Israelis and the
Americans think that once they give Iran
this little shove that people are going
to rise up and overthrow the regime,
that is not real life. We're going to be
seen as invaders and attackers and it's
going to unite Iranians against us and
to unite them against their Israeli
attackers.
Nothing good's going to come of this.
>> No, I agree with that. Uh, we have other
stuff to hit, too. Nicholas Franco, Ted,
would you say Afghanistan is a safer
place than Minneapolis right now?
Honestly, yeah. Under the Taliban,
that's the Afghanistan is safe. I mean,
really?
>> Yeah. Um,
by the way, we should talk about uh
Israel. So, Israel has reopened the
border crossing between uh between the
Gaza Strip and Egypt. uh the Rafa
crossing and um there's uh details are
are are thin but basically the Israelis
have been asked like well if uh first of
all it's for pedestrian traffic only.
>> Yes.
>> No no no vehicles.
>> Um why would that be? Is that just
because that way there's you don't have
it doesn't take as much time to inspect
people or
>> no no smuggling. They have to dismantle
every car coming in looking for for
weapons and ammunition. So, and then the
the thing is that for people leaving
Gaza, they're not being given any
assurances that they would be allowed to
return uh to uh the occupied territory
there. Um you know, if you're Gaza, if
you're Palestinian, you're probably not
taking this offer.
>> Yeah, I agree. They don't get anything
out of it. Okay. So, maybe they get to
go to Egypt for the day. What's to
what's to guarantee that the Israelis
are going to allow them back in?
I I I would say I'd be highly skeptical.
Highly. Um, thanks for the 20 bucks from
John Magcguire. 40 years of
manufacturing management and seuite. Um,
immigrants, legal or illegal, are not
taking your jobs now. It's automation
and AI. I look forward to seeing people
protesting robots.
>> Yeah, it's going to happen. That's the
future right there.
>> Yeah. I mean, statistically, it's
already happening. Yeah, for sure.
Um,
>> yeah.
>> I I wish I had glasses that attached to
my headphones. It'd be much easier. Um,
Robbie the n white nationalist says
Matthew C. Nobody protested Obama
because his policy wasn't violence
against US citizens. Go back to Europe,
Robbie.
>> Robbie, first of all, you better spell
Robbiey's name right. It's with a Y, not
an IIE. But, um, the thing is that his
Yeah. Well, I mean, that's true, right?
I mean, here's what's going on here.
What we need, we're we need like a few
rosy few rosy uh rosyfaced white uh you
know, Aryan babies to be killed by ICE
and the whole thing is going to fall
apart. I mean, that's what Americans
always need. YOU YOU AND I TALKED ABOUT
this for months. People are going to be
killed because of the way I comporting
itself. They're going to shoot people.
They're going to shoot Americans. And
predictably, they did. And they're going
to do it more. And uh and basically
that's the way American politics works.
You have to you need a martyr to get a
cause. And
>> that's absolutely true.
>> And and you know uh Renee Good wasn't
quite the right martyr at the right time
because you know the car was involved
and maybe she grazed or maybe even hit
the dude. Also she's a dyke. So like we
don't like that. But this guy oh you
just know at the White House they were
like ah [__] like, you know, he's like
a nice guy, thin, like I mean, they're
happy about the beard. I bet I bet they
liked that, but like otherwise they're
like, he's a young man and he's a nurse.
[__] he's an ICU nurse, works at the VA
hospital helping veterans. Probably the
killer for them was that video that
leaked of him leading the memorial
service for a fallen veteran. Um, and
and uh, you know, at the hospital and
it's like freedom isn't free. He's like
reading that whole thing. I'm like
thinking, "Oh, they're done for. Turn
them over. They're done."
>> That's right.
>> That is right.
>> Desert Fox, thanks for the five bucks.
Hey guys, longtime listener. Praying for
your pardon, John. And thank you for
your work, guys. What's your opinions on
Iran and the drum beat to war? I think
we kind of touched upon that, but we do
appreciate
>> I'm genuinely worried. I really am.
>> Thanks for the 20 bucks for your friend
John Mike from Mike and Noddingham.
John, did the CIA have any KPIs or
metrics that they used to measure
performance as in an officer? That's a
good question. I like it.
>> Um,
for for operations officers, case
officers, the the metrics were very
simply how many spies have you recruited
to steal secrets? I mean, if you
recruited some old lady to be a safe
housekeeper and make sure that the place
was clean and empty when you wanted it,
you know, for a for a clandestine
meeting, all right, yeah, maybe you get
a pat on the back, but you needed to
recruit genuine spies to steal foreign
secrets or genuine penetrations of
foreign um intelligence services or
foreign terrorist groups. That's that
was really the sole criterion.
>> Sounds like a good metric to me.
>> Yeah. Um so President Xi has and the top
leadership there in China is ousting a
lot of their uh top generals. Um I took
note of one factoid that was of great
interest to me parenthetically where
they said that um the mil the top
military brass has no combat experience
at this stage because they're too young
to have fought in the revolution. Now, I
will I'm going to use deploy. I'm going
to deploy that fact the next time
someone says that China represents a
military threat that like they haven't
done a war in so long that they don't
have any generals who know how to who
who have actual firsthand experience at
them.
>> Interesting. So, but anyway, um so
basically the um according to um a a
Chinese army mag uh newspaper editorial
um basically reading between the lines,
it looks like the guys who are on the
outs were considered not to have been
differential enough to the president in
China and that's why they were ousted.
You know, he's looking more for like
personal loyalty over
>> sort of institutional loyalty.
>> Yeah. Um, how important is this story?
>> I think it's u I think it's less
important in the near term, especially
here in the United States. I think it's
much more important over the long term
for the reasons that you cite. You know,
when it comes to to planning, military
planning, we're going to have to take
into consideration that there are no
senior generals with combat experience.
That's very important.
Um, just filming. Really? I heard with
the CI the money that the US sent to
Ukraine, they could have ended
homelessness three times over. Yeah,
that's true. The US spends more money on
harming people than helping people. And
then this bozo Robbie is crying about
immigrants.
That is true. Um, not that Robbie's a
bozo. I'm not going to say that's true
because I know that's not true. Um,
Matthew, sorry, but the current setup
for for illegal immigration is nearly
impossible. make an easier and
obtainable pathway that just doesn't
just favor those who can afford it.
Robbie is a white nationalist at heart.
No, he's a nationalist, not a white
>> nationalist.
>> Definitely a nationalist. Um
>> uh I agree. It's it's too hard to enter
the United States legally. I mean I mean
but we should be careful. We should just
be like admitting the good people. I
mean, you know, honestly, and you know,
I mean, this also, it's what's so
interesting to me the way that
Republicans have tried to turn a blind
eye to the story. Reminds me of the way
that Democrats ignored the Aurora,
Colorado, Trende Araua videos of those
>> terrifying men running through running
through the stairwells and knocking on
doors and with, you know, long guns
inside, you know, basically uh in public
housing or I'm not clear if that was
public housing or a private apartment
building, but it was it kind of was like
Democrats were like, "Well, that
building's been a piece of [__] for
years and this is so what." But it's
like, but the right was right about
that. I mean, it's ridiculous to have
like Venezuelan gangbangers running
around an apartment building in
Colorado. Um, and that should stop. And
now it's like Republicans find
themselves in the same boat. Like, you
guys look ridiculous when you're blaming
the guy who's just got 10 holes in his
back from ICE. You look stu you look
insane.
>> Agreed. Agreed.
Um, very quickly, uh, Rey, five bucks.
Thanks, John. Bought two of your books.
Um, how to disappear into in
surveillance. Listen to your life story
this weekend. I'm Pennsylvania born and
raised too, but on the south central
side, Eagles territory, praying for
pardon. And that will be the last word
today on deep program with Ted Rollins,
John Kiryaku. U please stay tuned. We'll
be back uh please to ti show with me and
Milo Chan. That's coming right up right
now. And uh please come back to tomorrow
morning and check out John and I at 9:00
am Eastern time for another episode.
Obviously, we'll be talking about
whatever happens for Minnesota and so
on. John, always great. Uh try to dig
out of the snow. Don't dig out too much,
though.
>> It's bad up there.
>> Just
>> Bye, everybody.
>> Let it go. Bye.